[
    {
        "question": "م ا ل ي و ي",
        "response": "ويليام"
    },
    {
        "question": "م ي ا ن",
        "response": "نامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ف ي ل و",
        "response": "لوفي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ي ن ي ر ا",
        "response": "ايرين"
    },
    {
        "question": "ت ا س ا",
        "response": "استا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ر و ت ا م ه",
        "response": "همتارو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ي ا ي ف و ال",
        "response": "الويفيا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ي ل و ن",
        "response": "نويل"
    },
    {
        "question": "ل ي ا ي ر",
        "response": "رايلي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ا ي ا ز د",
        "response": "دازاي"
    },
    {
        "question": "و ل ا",
        "response": "لاو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ر ا د ا م ا",
        "response": "مادارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ش ي ي ت و ر ي",
